Register of the Morris Childs papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Microfilm of Materials from the J. Edgar Hoover Foundation, 1924-1988 (Reels 1-33)
  - Miscellaneous materials, 1935-1978
    - Folder 259. Bulletin, note, serial issue, and tickets, 1967 (Reel 25)
    - Folder 260. Correspondence and printed matter relating to the firm Russian Language Specialties, 1963 (Reel 25)
    - Folder 261. Souvenir book commemorating the 75th birthday of Ella Reeve Bloor, 1937 (Reel 25)
    - Folder 262. Press releases from Panorama, the foreign press service of the German Democratic Republic, 1966-1967 (Reel 25)
  - Printed matter, 1924-1988
    Brochures, newsletters, pamphlets, and serial issues, largely relating to the Communist Party of the United States of America, other communist parties internationally, and radical movements in the United States.
    - Folder 263. Brochures and newsletters relating to Africa, 1935-1960 (Reel 25)
    - Folders 264-265. Ad Hoc Bulletin, 1963-1971 (Reel 25)
    - Serial issues and pamphlets, 1924-1988
      Arrangement Statement
      Arranged alphabetically by title.
      - Folder 266. A (Reel 26)
      - Folder 267. B-C (Reel 26)
      - Folders 268-269. D (Reel 26)
      - Folders 270-271. F (Reel 26)
      - Folder 272. I-L (Reel 27)
      - Folders 273-274. M (Reel 27)
      - Folder 275. N (Reel 27A)
      - Folders 276-278. P (Reels 27A, 28)
      - Folder 279. R-U (Reel 28)
      - Folders 280-281. W (Reel 28)
      - Folder 282. Y (Reel 28)
    - Pamphlets, monographs, and newsletters
      Arranged chronologically.
      - Folder 283. 1920s-1930s (Reel 28)
      - Folders 284-285. 1940s (Reel 29)
      - Folders 286-287. 1950s (Reel 30)
      - Folders 288-290. 1960s (Reels 31, 32)
      - Folders 291-294. 1970s (Reels 32, 33)